Guide to the New York State AFL-CIO Records WAG.031
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - Benefore Properties, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Black Trade Unionists, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Biltman and King, 1986-1988 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Blood Program, Apprentice Blood Drive, 1984-1989 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Blue Cross, Blue Shield, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Boiler Makers, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1986-1988 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Bosky, Ivan, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Bogus Labor Directory, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Boston Harbor Case, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Bottle Bill, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Bork, NY Coalition Against, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Boycotts, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Boycott of Consumers Union, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Bricklayers Local 85, 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Brach, William, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Brooklyn Army Terminal, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Brooklyn Ecumenical Cooperative, 1985-1988 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Navy Yard Jobs, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Sports Foundation, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Union Gas Company, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Broome County Federation of Labor, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Bronx Borough President, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Budget Proposals Affecting Urban Areas, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Building and Construction Trade Council, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - NYS 1982 Convention (photos) (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo Health Care Clinics, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Building and Construction Trade, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Building and Construction Aids Council: Audits and Correspondence, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Building and Construction Aids Council: Audits and Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Bureau of National Affairs, 1984-1987 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Bureau of Public Affairs, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Business Council of New York State, 1984-1991 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Business Trends in New York State, 1985-1988 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Small Business Report, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Greater New York Real Estate Forum By-laws (BCTC), 1982 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Butler, Walter, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - California Employment and Training, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - California Federation of Labor, 1987-1991 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Canada and the U.S. Columbia University Assembly, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Canadian Energy, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Canadian Consulate General, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Capitol Examiner, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Capitol Newspapers, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Cardinals Committee, 1984-1992 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Career Centers, NY State, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Carey, Reverend Phillip: Xavier Institute, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Cargo Preference, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Carpenters, United Brotherhood of Carpenters, 1983-1994 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Carrier Corporation 1986 Layoffs Catholic Charities of Brooklyn, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Catholic Tradition and Social Change, lecture by Senator Moinahan, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Catholic Guardian Society, 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Catholic Interracial Council of NY, 1984-1987 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Center for Labor and Urban Programs (Binstock Brochure), undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Center for Labor and Industrial Relations, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Central Labor Council, CLCs meeting 1993 (evaluations), undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Albany Central Federation for Labor, 1987-1990 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Auburn Area Council, undated (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Broome County Federation of Labor, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo AFL-CIO Council, 1985-1993 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Cattaragus-Allegahny Labor Council, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Central NY Labor Council, 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Chemunt County Labor Council, 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Duchess County CLC, undated (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Geneva Federation of Labor, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Glenn Falls CLC, 1990-1994 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Greater Syracuse CLC, 1986-1991 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Hudson Catskills CLC, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Jamestown Asia CLC, 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Jefferson Lewis, St. Lawrence Labor Councils, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Long Island Federation of Labor, 1986-1988 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Mid-State CLC, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Northeastern NY CLC, 1985-1992 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - YC CLC, 1986-1992 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Orange County CLC, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Oswego County CLC, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Rochester CLC, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Rockland County, 1986-1992 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Schenectady Area CLC, 1988-1993 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Steuben County Labor Council, 1986-1992 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Syracuse CLC Tri-County, 1987-1989 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Troy Area Labor Council, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Upper Hudson Area, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Westchester-Putnam Counties, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - CLC By-laws and Constitution, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Central Labor Council Membership Meetings, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - CLC Correspondence (outgoing), 1984-1992 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Central Labor Rehabilitation Council, 1987-1992 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Central for Women and Government, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Central America-Labor and International Affairs Conference, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Central American Trade Unionists Reception, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Change New York, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Changing Role of Labor, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Child Labor, 1988-1990 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Census, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - NY City Charter Revision, undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - The Changing Situation of Workers and their Union, AFL-CIO Committee on the Evolution of Work, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - On Site Child Care Privatization, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Federation of Labor, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Federation of Labor, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Chris Craft Inc. Layoff, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - City Corp Presenting Center, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - City Project, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - CBS Takeover by Turner Broadcasting: Citizens Organize to Restore an Effective Corporate Tax C.O.R.E.C.T., 1985 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Citizens for Tax Justice, 1985-1990 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - City of Hope, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - City University of New York: Vocation Education Advisory Council, 1987-1990 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Civil Eights Conference AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Civil Rights Legislative Memorandum (Ludwig Jaffee), 1977 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Civil Service Employees Association, 1985-1994 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Civil Service Technical Guild, School Buildings, 1985-1988 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Clean Indoor Air Act, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Clean Water Act, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Cleary, E.J. Congratulations Letters, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Cleary, E.J. Personal, 1974; 1983-1986 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Cleveland AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Coastal Zone Management, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Collective Bargaining Institute, undated (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Coalition Against Double Taxation, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Coalition of Safe Government, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Council of Great Lakes Governor, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Coalition in Black Trade Unionists, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Congressional Research Service: Labor Issues and the 10th Congress, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Connecticut State AFL-CIO, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Congressional Delegation, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Coalition for Border Security, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Coalition on Economic Priority, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Coalition of North Eastern Governor, 1986-1988 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Record, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Coalition of Labor Movement, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Report on the Plight of Collective Bargaining System: Assemblyman Frank Barbaro, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Colleran OHara and Mills, Attorneys, 1978-1992 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Color Me Union Training Series, CLUW, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Colt Industries Strike, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Columbia University: Seminar on Labor, 1985-1987 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Assembly Labor Committee, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Committee of Interns and Residents, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Committee for International Support of Trade Union Rights, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Communication Workers of America, 1988-1993 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Community Service Work: Prison Inmates, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - California Contracts, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Clinton, Bill President, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Compact for Learning, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Comstock, Q and Co., Inc., 1985 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Conference on Partnerships, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Connecticut State AFL-CIO, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Consortium for Worker Education, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Contractors of America, 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Contracting Out, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Construction and Building Industry, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Construction Women and Minorities, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Cope Capitols, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Coors Boycott, 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Coro Foundation, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Copies of Mailgrams and Telegrams, 1981-1988 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Cornell University Catherwood Library Construction Project, undated (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - CCC News, Construction Coordinating Committees, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Corporate Takeover Bill, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Correctional Institutes, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Courage Foundation, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Contracting Out Court Case, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Cuomo Appointments, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Cuomo, Mario, 1985-1989 (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - SABA, School and Business Alliance (Pataki), 1994 (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - Corogan Associates, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - Council of Business and Labor for New York, undated (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - Gerald Crotty, Secretary to Governor, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 44)
  - Organized Crime Task Force, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 45)
  - Governor Cuomo: Press Releases, 1987-1991 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - CUNY, City University of New York, 1985-1991 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Labor Leaders Management with Governor Cuomo, 1990-1992 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - New York State Dairy Farmers, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Alphonse DAmato, 1991-1995 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Daily News, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Tribute Co., Subsidiary of Daily News, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Daily News: Corporate Campaign, undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - David Island Project, 1990-1995 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Days Inn, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Deborah Hospital, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Deductibility of State and Local Taxes, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Delaware State DOL Division of Training Employment and Training, 1987-1995 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Delwood Foods, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Delta Dental, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Democratic Policy Commission, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Democrats, 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Democratic National Convention 1988, 1988-1990 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Walter Mondale 1984 Election (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - July 15, 1984 Pre-Convention Reception (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Rebuilding the Democratic Party: A Matter of Principles, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - NY State Democratic Committee Dinner, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Letters, Articles, Etc. to be read, 1984-1985 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Disinflation and the Decline of Unions, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - July 15, 1984 March and Demonstration: San Francisco Labor Council (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Invitations to Receptions: Schedule of Events for Week, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - 1984 Democratic National Convention Correspondence, 1984-1992 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Department for Professional Employees, 1984-1992 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Democratic Campaign 1984 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Dinkins, David Mayor, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Detroit Newspaper Strike, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Dislocated Workers: Canada National Association, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Dislocation and Worker Adjustment Assistance Act of 1988 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - DC #37 AFSCME 40th Anniversary, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Biennial Education Conference DC #37, June 13-20, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Joe Doherty, 1989-1990 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Dole vs. Dow, 1988-1990 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Dollars Against Diabetes, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Dominos Pizza, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Dredging, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Drexel University, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Drug Testing, 1986-1989 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Dunkirk Ice Cream, 1984-1989 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Dunlop Commission, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Dunlop Tire Corp., 1988 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Eastern Airlines, Frank Lorenzo, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Eastcon 85, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Eastern Seaboard Apprentice Conference, 1984-1989 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Economic Conversion, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Economic Cooperation in the Pacific Basin, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Minutes of Meeting of the Economic Development Subcommittee, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Economic Development, 1987-1993 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Economic Indicators, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Economy (Inflation), 1993 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Economic Policy Council of the United Nations, Association of the USA, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Economic Research, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Economic Report, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Americas Changing Economic Landscape, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Edgehill-Newport, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Education, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Education Committee NY State AFL-CIO, 1985-1990 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Education and Cultural Fund of the Electrical Industry, 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1991-1992 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Education Questionnaire for Convention Delegates, undated (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Electrical Contractors, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Effective Trusteeship: Association of Governing Board of Universities and Colleges, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Elevator Industry Apprentices, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Ellis Island, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Local 463 IUE, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Empire State College, 1994-1995 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Empire Plan Lawsuit Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Empire Plan, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Empire Plan, 1987-1988 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Empire State Union Housing Trust by Amivest Corporation, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Empire State Report, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Empire State Weekly, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Empire State Veterans, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Employee Assistance Programs Outside, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Employee Ownership, 1986-1991 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - NYUS Energy Planning, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - National Journal, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Equitable Benefit Insurance Services, Inc., 1990 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - 21st Century Environmental Quality Bond Act, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - NY State Environmental Conservation Directory, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Environmental Protection, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Executive Budget Presentation, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Environmental Conservation, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Exxon Corporation, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Statement of Era Working Group, undated (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - NY State Code of Ethics, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Fair Labor Standards Amendments of 1985 Conference Report (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Family Leave, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Family Security Act of 1987 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Farm Workers, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - FAST, Food Allied Services Trades, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Surface Transportation Act and Uniform Relocation Assistance Act, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Federal Labor Laws, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Federal Election Committee, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of NY, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Federal Tax Reform / Deficit Reduction, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Financial Services Corporation of NY City, undated (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Federal Tax Reform, 1986-1995 (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Geraldine Ferraro, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - The Financial Page Newsletter, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Fire Officers Association, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Fire Safety Standards: Toxicity Data Bank, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Florida Building and Construction Trade Council, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Florida Labor Management Council, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - For a Change Publication, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Investments, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Trade, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Foundation Directory of Grants, undated (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Four Winds Hospital, Connecticut, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Free Trade Agreement: United States and Mexico Fast Track, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Friends of Mario Cuomo Committee, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Fund for Open Information and Accountability, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Future Planning Association, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - GATT, General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, 1984-1994 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - General Contractors Association of NY, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - General Electric, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - General Service Administration, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - General Vision, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Generic Pharmaceutical Industry Association, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Gephardt Amendment, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - West Germany, undated (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Gimbels Closing, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Samuel Gompers Stamp Club, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Edward S. Gordon Company, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Gotbaum, Victor: Columbia University, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Governors Office of Regulatory Reform, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Greater Green Fall Central Labor Council, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Greater NY Blood Plan: Ed Cleary, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Greater NY Joint Council, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Greater NY Safety Council, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Greyhound Strike, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Guatemala IUF Trade Union Delegation, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - Hanford Atomic Metal Trades Council, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Hard Choices: Summary Report of National Infrastructure Study, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Reform of Hatch Act, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Hart, Gary Senator, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Hazard Abatement Board, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Health Care Reform, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - Health Care Reform, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - Health and Safety, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - Health Hazard Information, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - Health Plans, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 47)
  - Allen G. Hevesi Comptroller, 1995-1996 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Health Systems Agency of NE New York, 1984-1987 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Hess Oil, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Highway & Mass Transit Authority Bill, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Historical Records in the Empire State, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Higher Education Daily, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Histadrut, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Hobbs Act, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - The Homeless, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Hotel / Restaurant Employees Local 6 H.E.R.E.I.U., 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Committee for Housing NY, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Citizens Action for Affordable Housing, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Housing Investment Fund, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Housing Development Corp.: Not for Profit Low Income Housing, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Housing Investment Trust, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Hotel, Motel, Restaurant Employees & Bartenders Union, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - NY Hotel and Motel Trades Council, 1989-1991 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Hynes, Charles, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Union Hotels, 1989-1992 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Hudson Valley Labor Council, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Hudacs, John, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Human Rights Article, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Hungary, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Hynes, Joe District Attorney, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Immigration Law, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilders Workers of America, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - The Infrastructure Trust Fund, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - IUE District Three, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - John Iacco: Governor Cuomos Office, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - IAM, District 100 Strike Against E1 A1 Airlines, JFK Airport, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - Illinois State AFL-CIO, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - I.B.E.W. Joint Board of the Electric Industry, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - I.B.E.W. Local 3, 1983-1985 (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - Independent Contractors, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - Independent Federation of Flight Attendants, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 36)
  - Independent Savings Bank, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 37)
  - Industrial Relations Research Association, 1984-1987 (Box 66, Folder 38)
  - Inductive Relief, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 39)
  - Institute of International Debt and Development, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 40)
  - International Association of Personnel in Employment Security, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 41)
  - Institute for Socioeconomic Studies, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 42)
  - Insurance Workers International Union, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 43)
  - Interim Steering for the Steuben County Labor Council, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 44)
  - Institute for Meditation and Conflict Resolution, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 45)
  - Interface, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 46)
  - IBEW Local #3, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 47)
  - Industrial Development Agency, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 48)
  - International, 1986-1988 (Box 66, Folder 49)
  - Interim Crime Task Force Report, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 50)
  - IATSE International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Equipment, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 51)
  - IBEW Local 1409, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 52)
  - ICA Group, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 53)
  - Independent Contractor Bill, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 54)
  - International Labor Organization, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 55)
  - Israel Bonds (luncheon), 1990 (Box 66, Folder 56)
  - ILGWU Sketchbook, 1958 (Box 66, Folder 57)
  - Institute of Collective Bargaining, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 58)
  - International Association of Mechanics and Aerospace Workers, 1984-1992 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - IAIABC Convention, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - International Institute for Economic Research, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - International Leather Goods Plastics and Novelty Workers Union, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - International Society for Retirement Planning, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - International Typographical Union, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - International Union of Police Associations, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Internet, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Investments, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Irish Arts Center, 1986-1988 (Box 67, Folder 11)